{
    "subject": "resource/Turn_10_Studios",
    "predicate": "property/foundation",
    "object": "2001",
    "human_readable": "Turn 10 Studios was founded in 2001.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9019997715950012,
            "question": "When was Turn 10 Studios founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8908405303955078,
            "question": "Who are the founders of Turn 10 Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6536442637443542,
            "question": "What year did Turn 10 Studios begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6025566458702087,
            "question": "Where is Turn 10 Studios headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5375487208366394,
            "question": "In what industry is Turn 10 Studios involved?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43745192885398865,
            "question": "What impact has Turn 10 Studios had on its industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39991554617881775,
            "question": "Is Turn 10 Studios a relatively new company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27397075295448303,
            "question": "What type of products or services does Turn 10 Studios create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2708578407764435,
            "question": "Does Turn 10 Studios collaborate with other companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2228539139032364,
            "question": "Has Turn 10 Studios won any awards for its work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Turn 10 Studios was founded in 2001.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6183_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Turn 10 Studios collaborate with other companies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6183_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of products or services does Turn 10 Studios create?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6183_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Turn 10 Studios a relatively new company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6183_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6183_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the triple \"Turn 10 Studios was founded in 2001\" is supported by the context information provided, which includes multiple documents stating that Turn 10 Studios was established in 2001."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the documents provided, which state \"Turn 10 Studios was founded in 2001,\" directly supporting the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}